我知道这段感情的走向
I know what it is, where it's going.
杰克是个好人  可是
Jake is a nice guy, but...
这样下去不会有结果  我早已心知肚明
it's not going anywhere. I've known this for a while now.
也许明知无路可走
Maybe it's human nature to keep going
却仍继续下去是人类的天性
in the face of this knowledge.
另一条路需要太多精力
The alternative requires too much energy.
还有果断
Decisiveness.
人们停留在不合适的关系中  只因这样更轻松
People stay in unhealthy relationships because it's easier.
基础物理
Basic physics.
运动物体具有惯性
An object in motion tends to stay in motion.
人们倾向于维系早该结束的关系
People tend to stay in relationships past their expiration date.
牛顿情感第一定律
It's Newton's first law of emotion.
你想下车喝杯咖啡  吃点东西吗
Do you want to stop for a coffee or something, a... a snack?